National Society United States Daughters of 1812, District of Columbia Society 115
People's Archive, MLK Library
National Society United States Daughters of 1812, District of Columbia Society
1923-1958
People's Archive, MLK Library
National Society, United States Daughters of 1812. District of Columbia Society
115
0.25 Linear feet
1 Boxes
Arrangement
Processed without series.
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1892, the National Society of the United States Daughters of 1812 is a service organization for women focused on promoting patriotism, preserving and promoting the legacy of the early American people, especially between the end of the American Revolution and the War of 1812. The Society was incorporated on February 25, 1901 by an Act of the United State Congress.
Custodial History
Provenence unknown.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of yearbooks, by-laws, clippings, a banquet invitation, and a program.
Women; Societies and clubs; Yearbooks; Organizational Records; Ephemera; Social groups
- Series 1
  - Yearbook, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yearbook, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Yearbook, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Yearbook (2 copies), 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Yearbook, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Yearbook, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Yearbook, 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Yearbook, 1952-1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Yearbook, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - By-Laws, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - By-Laws, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1931-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Program, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Invitations, 1940-1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)